

### Sina ABBASI

Student at Guilan University | Teacher Assistant at University of Guilan

- Rasht, Guilan
- ☑ sinaabbasi@gmail.com
- **&** +98-902-345-6789

### SOCIAL

- in @Sina-Abbasi
- ♠ @1SinaAbbasi
- © Currently Disabled!!

### PROFILE

I want to learn and learn and learn. Understanding the universe can't wait. Intelligence of human beings is the source and artificial intelligence is the key. We must continue our ancestors progress to make a better world. I am at the beginning of my road to be an AI researcher.

### EDUCATION

Guilan University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering 2017 - 2021

### SKILLS

- Python
- Java
- HTML / CSS
- Microsoft
- English

  - Translation
- MySQL
- - Word
- Microsoft **Power Point**

### EXPERIENCE

# Formal Languages and Automata Teacher Assistant

Jan 2021 - Present | University of Guilan

- Held online classes in order to train students.
- Designing assignments.
- Assessment of students assignments.

# Digital Circuits Teacher Assistant

Jan 2021 - Present | University of Guilan

- Assessment of students assignments.

### CERTIFICATES

# Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) (2020)

An online non-credit course authorized by University of Michigan and offered through Coursera.

## Python Data Structures (2020)

An online non-credit course authorized by University of Michigan and offered through Coursera.

#### LANGUAGES

 Persian English Italian

### INTERESTS

8 X Travel **Motion Pictures** Music Read **(** 4 Football **Fitness**